<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hi, I&#39;m Thesi</title>
    <link>http://thesipham1401.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Hi, I&#39;m Thesi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 May 2020 22:52:27 +0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://thesipham1401.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Week After Quarantine</title>
      <link>http://thesipham1401.github.io/story/the-week-after-quarantine/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 May 2020 22:52:27 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://thesipham1401.github.io/story/the-week-after-quarantine/</guid>
      <description>Hello every, It&amp;rsquo;s me again. I had a long study week at my university. It was fun to meet my classmate &amp;lsquo;cause I have two months on my room. This was great to interact my teachers in a real life, because I was boring with sit in front the screen all day to watch livestream and self-study. At that time, I proposed myself to self-study Javascript, HTML, CSS and PHP. However, the result is really bad, I played game the whole time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Volunteer Trip, Long An</title>
      <link>http://thesipham1401.github.io/story/volunteer-triplong-an/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 May 2020 21:34:27 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://thesipham1401.github.io/story/volunteer-triplong-an/</guid>
      <description>Xin chào các bạn, lại là mình đây. Hôm nay là một ngày cuối tuần, hẵn ai cũng có dự định đi đâu thoải mái đầu óc hay là ở nhà chill out đúng không. Hôm nay là ngày cuối cùng của kì nghỉ tết dài nhất lịch sử nên mình quyết định đi tham gia một chương trình của Quán Cơm 2000, có tên là Trao Yêu Thương Về Miền Tây cùng với 2 homies và eny mình.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quadrature Phase Shift Keying </title>
      <link>http://thesipham1401.github.io/project/qpsk/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2020 22:33:53 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://thesipham1401.github.io/project/qpsk/</guid>
      <description>Xin chào các bạn, học kì vừa rồi mình có học môn Digital Signal Processing Labs của Prof.Dr Lê Tiến Thường. Môn này cũng hơi khó bởi vì có rất ít tài liệu và tự lực cánh sinh là chủ yếu, môn này làm quen với mạch TMS320C5515 eZDSP USB Stick Development Tool. Làm quen ở đây là làm như project nhỏ như đây chữ lên màn hình OLED, led blind, FFT,&amp;hellip; Và bài tập lớn có nhiều chủ đề, và nhóm mình gồm 2 người bốc trúng chủ đề khó nhất (Prof nói vậy), là xuất tín hiệu QPSK từ con C5515 ra Code Composer Studio.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Preface</title>
      <link>http://thesipham1401.github.io/story/mylife-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2020 22:29:40 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://thesipham1401.github.io/story/mylife-1/</guid>
      <description>Xin chào các bạn, hôm nay mình tập viết blog để lưu lại những kiến thức cũng như chia sẻ những khoảng khắc của mình. Đây là blog đâu tiên của mình và mình vẫn còn đang học thêm về static site. Chủ yếu blog của mình viết về xoay quanh mình, nên hiện tại mình đang làm quen với IoT và cố gắng ra trường sớm nhất :D</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy Birthday to my girlfriend</title>
      <link>http://thesipham1401.github.io/posts/hpbd/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 May 2020 21:53:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://thesipham1401.github.io/posts/hpbd/</guid>
      <description>Hihi. Hope you like my present, which was the thing I hear from you :D. It plus a bonus of 3000 loves. We have a great time together. When I met you, I learned numerous things, especially love, charity and mature. Wishing you dream to guide your path. We was head over heels. and now, I&amp;rsquo;d like have a couple offspring like you said xD. I love 3000 times.
I feel quite sad &amp;lsquo;cause it isn&amp;rsquo;t perfect gift :(</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>